I was told up to 15% allowance, but after that it doesn't matter as long as you give me the number of times.
Kei también
Hello, I am Kakihara from Nogizaka46
I am Reno Nakamura
I am Teresa Ikeda
Let me tell you where we are.
Ta-da!
Wow!
We are at Osaka Castle Hall!
We have a panel here. I've never seen them this close before.
It's hard to come by, isn't it? They don't come this way.
It's strange that I'm here.
We start our summer national tour tomorrow.
Big?
We'll be at Osaka Park for the Midsummer National Tour.
So we came one step ahead of you.
Why did we come?
What shall we eat at the national tour in Osaka?
Wow!
Although I'm from Tochigi, I was born in Osaka.
Oh, I didn't know that.
I lived in Osaka until I was about 10.
You've lived here for quite a while.
I spent about half of my life in Osaka.
This time I asked my aunt if she'd come to Osaka, and she said, "Go eat this.
I'm looking forward to it!
I got a letter from her.
I'll read it!
I recommend lunch at Osteria Rave!
I went there for lunch and thought everything from the ingredients to the flavors to the performance of the food being made right in front of you was wonderful!
It's a lovely looking and tasty experience, and I'm excited to see what comes out next!
It's a place that makes you think that whatever you eat will be absolutely delicious!
I can't wait to see what they have in store for us!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm so happy!
I'm so glad I got your letter.It was a pleasure to write to you.
Thank you very much.
I'll write in this column.
Osteria
Seino
Since you've come all the way to Osaka for the tour
Let's have lunch at Osteria Rave!
Looks spicy!
Too spicy!
I want to eat it!
We're on our way to the restaurant now.
Have you been to the restaurant you just introduced?
Probably not.
First time? Then it's the first time for all of us.
I'm so excited!
Italia.
You said lunch, so I don't know what it is.
You're right.
I'm looking forward to it.
I had this image of Osaka as being famous for its powdered food.
So I thought, "Oh, it's Italian food in Osaka!
It's true that you have to be a local.
That's true.
I'm really looking forward to it!
So we came close to the restaurant...
I can see it now.
I wonder if that's it.
This must be it.
This is it.
Isterianave.
Yay!
The store is so stylish!Stylish store
Such a stylish store.
I wouldn't go in there at all.
Ha-ha-ha!
I heard the lunch here is really good.
Yes, ma'am.
Can I ask them to order lunch for me?
Yes, of course.
Just the ingredients in front of me look delicious!
Hey, octopus!
Octopus is amazing.
This is amazing.
Can I have a little piece of this?
A whole octopus.
Octopus round and round.
Oh, you pushed it.
Wow.
So powerful!
Today, I'm going to prepare it with, uh, risotto.
Uh...
What kind of risotto would you like?
Risotto with tomatoes.
Or risotto with octopus.
Yes...
Sounds delicious.
Wow.
Everything looks delicious.
Ew.
Then I guess that means I can eat all three kinds one at a time.
Oh, you can do that?
You can do that too.
Okay, then.
Okay, bye.Okay, then.
Leave it to me.
I'll leave it to you.
Eat here today.
We can work hard tomorrow.
We have to work hard tomorrow.
We have to do our best, right?
I think I'm losing strength.
You're lying.
But we're the same age.
But now, Nasa-chan...
You've certainly changed.
You haven't changed at all.
But you've got the cankles... and the strength.
No, I mean, you're still in high school.
If you keep going the same way...
Oh, I can't do it anymore.
I can't see...
I can't see at all.
Oh, you can't see me at all?
No, I was already aghast at the immediate question.
"Uh-oh!
"Aaah!
[ED]
Thank you so much. Thank you so much. All the judgments are not at the level of all the judgments.
Wow.
Wow, that's a little fancy.
There are flowers, too.
Oh, no, here it comes!
Let's eat it!
I don't know where to start.
There were too many!
These onions are so tempting!
Let's eat!
Yum!
Delicious!Delicious!
Delicious!
Sweet!
Sweet?
I'll start with the salad.
Bon appétit!
Luscious!
Lush.
Tasty?
It's delicious.
Good.
I'll take this tomato.
Bon appétit.
It's like...
It's sweet like a fruit.
Oh, really?
It's so sweet!
Yes, the onions are sweet!
Onions are so good!
It's so simple.
Bake the onions right here in the oven.
You're baking them.
Bake them slowly for about an hour.
Then they're so sweet.
It's so sweet and melty.
The potatoes are slightly curry-like.
It tastes a little like curry.
It's a little more curry-like today
What is this?
It's manganjishito!
From Kyoto.
Manganji chili pepper.
It's very common in Italy.
I see.
It's a summer vegetable.Summer Vegetables.
Summer vegetables?
The atmosphere changes with the seasons.
Let's try them
Tomatoes are the best anywhere
We have tomatoes.
They are so delicious!
What's the best of the north in Hokkaido
The best of the north.
It's the best of both worlds.
They've gone to the extreme, right?
It's a lot of food, but...
Is it still an appetizer?
Usually.
Do you eat out?
I don't.
Sometimes.
If they ask me out.
Sometimes, really.
After rehearsal.
I don't eat out at all.
So you cook for yourself?
I cook for myself.
I don't cook for myself that much.
Oh, really?
I don't know what I'm eating.
What do you eat to be so thin?
So, how is Ren?
We get along really well.
The kotatsu and the members.
We get along well.
Kotatsu and the members.
We have dinner all the time.
What do you eat?
It depends on the day.It depends on the day.
Sometimes it's yakiniku.
Or an Italian place that looks like it's run by a private individual.
Or an Italian restaurant.
I go to all kinds of places.
Gourmet food.
But, you know, not at all.
I also really like family restaurants.
We all say, "Let's go there.
He's so cute.
He's really messing things up.
I can do it now.
I did it.
I can do it in about 10 minutes.
I'm excited.
Tomato.
Yprin
I left it to 3 different resorts today!
Wow.
Thank you very much.
I used basil.
Thank you.
Tomato and scallop resort.
Wow.
Cute!
Thank you.
Wow.
Wow! The plate is so cute!
It's so cute! It's got fish in it!
It's an Italian plate.
An Italian plate.
What?What?
Oh, Gun-chan.
I can't help it.
All of you.
Wow!
This is the corn one.
In Italy, risotto is eaten with a fork, not a spoon.
Oh, they eat it with a fork?
Fruit tomatoes with a fork.
Risotto.
And then there's the risotto with sago and basil.
Yum. Yum.
Delicious!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
What shall we do with it? This.
Do you want to share?
Let's share.
Shall we pass around a small plate?
Sure, let's put it in there.
Smart, smart, smart.
That's what I'm talking about.
Divided. - Divided.
Divided.
We've got it, we've got it.
Bon appétit.
You eat it with a fork?
It tastes better with a fork.
Frisch tomatoes.
Sweet.
Sweet?
This is good. This is good.
Wow, that looks good.
I'm chewing on it.
It's a full-body deliciousness.
This octopus.This octopus
The octopus is huge.
The octopus is so big!
Bon appétit!
Hmm?
It's so soft!
Ehhhh...
Hey, the octopus!
You scared me.
Daddy...
The octopus is so plump!
Wow!
Is that the octopus from earlier?
It was here.
Yes, the morning before.
Oh, Maecho.
I'm cooking with freshly boiled water
Wow, a whole bunch
I was here a while ago
So, the octopus I went to
I've got a craving
in our stomachs.
Then we'll have the corn
Corn.
Yes, sir.
Bon appétit!
Wow!
This one has a great corn texture.
Oh, yeah, it's amazing.
It's like when you bite into that corn.
It's like you just bit into the corn.
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
It's corn!
It's amazing, isn't it?
Octopus is soft.
Everyone!Everyone
Sweet tomatoes.
Wow.
Delicious.
I want to take some home.
I want to eat it every day.
I want to eat it.
Then I'll make it every day.
It's too much work for the manager.
It's delicious.
Oooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo....
It was so delicious. Thank you for the food.
I did get to know a few great places, though,
I've actually heard of one more recommendation,
One more thing?
Yes, one more thing.
Takoyaki 18 Takoyaki.
I have been going to this place for a long time,
After pouring the dough onto the griddle, the amount of dregs poured generously and generously.
The whole surface of the takoyaki is a sea of dregs, making you wonder if the takoyaki will really turn into a round takoyaki.
From there, he used a pick in each hand,
The takoyaki are made in the blink of an eye at the speed of an oni (a handheld takoyaki pick).
The crunchy texture of the freshly made takoyaki is the most delicious.
Osaka's unique flavor is here.
It was takoyaki.
Osaka is all about takoyaki.
That's right, I have an image of it.
It fits perfectly.
Perfect.
It fits.
Read it, read it. I just read it.
Since you've come all the way to Osaka for the tour, go eat takoyaki from Takoyaki 18.
It looks like it's almost there.
Here we are.
Number 18.No. 18.
Number 18.
Ochata.
Sorry to bother you.
Ojama-sama shimasu.
Welcome, please come in.
Sorry.
Here you go.
I heard that the takoyaki at this restaurant is delicious and full of tenkasu,
May I ask for your recommendation?
What do you recommend?
We have a lot of flavors.
We have a regular menu here, but there are a lot of tenkasu,
I would like you to eat it with salt,
If you like it, you can have it with more tenkasu than if it were only for me.
If you like age, age more.
Let's ask for it.
The salt is delicious.
No, I'm sure it's good.
I can make it just for myself according to my taste,
I see.
I'll check the taste with three, three, four pieces, and then I'll ask you to share the salt from the sauce, which will be shared with me in a casual way.
Then, that's it.
Yes, you can make it to your liking.
Yes, please.
The takoyaki are cooking right now.
Wow, it's red!
Red!
Why is it so red?
I wonder what it is.
What's red?
This is ground shrimp.
Shrimp.
I see. So they're prawns.
The tenkasu.
Wow, it's not as hot as I thought?Wow, wow, it's not as hot as I thought?
I can't see it anymore. It's really a sea of dregs down there.
Wow!
Wow, amazing!
Amazing!
Wow, it's so fast! It's so fast, and it's so beautiful!
It's so fast and so beautiful!
I can feel Osaka! It's so nice! It smells so good!
Thank you. Let me give it to you.
Wow!
Steam's coming out!
Wow! Amazing!
Thank you.
It's heavenly and cute.
So cute.
Bon appétit!
Excuse me for the sake.
But of course! Can I say "salt"?
I was wondering about that earlier.
Let's go.
How much of what?
A little... this much.
It looks hot.
I don't know if I can eat this.
Careful, it's definitely hot!
It's definitely hot. I can't take a bite.
I can't take a bite.
I can't take a bite. I have cat's tongue, right?
I can see the steam from here.
I can see it.
Bon appétit!
It looks hot!
It's hot.
It is, isn't it?
The tenkasu is crunchy.
But still tender.But it was tender.
Oh, my God.
And the box is firm. It's, uh... it's delicious.
It's good. Really?
What flavor do you want, Teresa?
No, I'm going to go with...
Pentacin? Pentacin.
Looks hot.
Oh, there you go.
You got it.
It's all gone.
Fluffy.
You look hot.
I don't know what you're saying.
I put too much in.
Looks delicious.
It has a gentle taste.
It's dashi, isn't it?
The broth is delicious.
Is it hot?
Is it okay?
The broth is cold.
I see.
Just right.
Okay, I'll try the flat smile.
That's great!
I can feel it when I grab it with chopsticks.
It's fluffy.
That's great.
It's kind of fluffy.
Looks like...
This mayonnaise
It's thin!
It's a thin one!
Cute tongs!
Cute takoyaki!Cute this takoyaki
Only one
Only one is on this takoyaki, so cute!
Now, let's eat!
Wow!
Look, look, it's amazing!
Bon appétit!
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Mmmm...
Oh, it looks delicious!
Looks delicious!
You know, takoyaki in Tokyo...
Most of them are crunchy.
Deep fried.
This is amazing!
So fluffy!
Soft and fluffy.
But the tempeh has a certain presence.
I don't know...
It's fluffy, but it also has a crunchy texture.
but it also has a crunchy texture.
It's a perfect balance.
It's so delicious!
I can't get enough of the soup stock.
I can't get enough of it.
I'm so happy!
So happy!
I want a second one.
I heard that eating takoyaki brings good luck.
Oh, really?
That's why we're all so lucky right now.
Wow, that's great!
Yay!
Before the show.
Everybody's spirits are up.We're all getting lucky.
Yay!
We ate and got lucky.
Wow.
Salt is delicious.
Really?
Mmm.
Wow.
Takoyaki from Takoyaki No. 18 Service.
Thank you for the food!
It was delicious!
Yes, so we enjoyed Osaka's gourmet food a lot!
Yes, it was delicious!
It was delicious!
I'm going to do my best at the concert tomorrow!
Yes!
Yes, I will!
Please subscribe to our channel.
Yes, ma'am.